[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these was the name of a London street which housed a prison?", "correct_answer": "Clink", "incorrect_answers": ["Brailey", "Gow", "Gaol"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "War of the Worlds is the 1953 film adaptation of Orson Wells famous radio broadcast based on H. G. Wells popular novel.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vitamin C is a powerful antioxidant and pro-oxidant.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what famous math problem, first posed in the 18th century by a French mathematician, is pi involved?", "correct_answer": "Buffons Needle Problem", "incorrect_answers": ["The travelling salesman problem", "Zenos Paradox of the Tortoise", "Zenos Paradox of Achilles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the tiny new workers in Willy Wonkas factory in te 2005 movie Charlie and the Chocolate Factory?", "correct_answer": "Oompa-Loompas", "incorrect_answers": ["Cocco-Boccos", "Lilliputians", "Pertroblisamians"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does DC stand for in the comic which first introduced Batman?", "correct_answer": "Detective Comics", "incorrect_answers": ["Direct Choice", "Dancing Candles", "Daily Choice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first major North American root beer to contain caffeine?", "correct_answer": "Barqs", "incorrect_answers": ["Triple XXX", "A-Treat", "Frostie Root Beer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What number does the Roman Numeral L represent?", "correct_answer": "50", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "5000", "500"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Woodrow Wilson (the USA), Georges Clemenceau (France) and David Lloyd George (Great Britain) signed a treaty of global importance. Which was the treaty?", "correct_answer": "Treaty of Versailles", "incorrect_answers": ["Treaty of Brest-Litovsk", "Treaty of Berlin", "Treaty of San Stefano"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was the dodo discovered?", "correct_answer": "1598", "incorrect_answers": ["1627", "1605", "1681"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The theory of relativity was introduced in physics by this man.", "correct_answer": "Albert Einstein", "incorrect_answers": ["Galileo Galilei", "Archimedes", "Isaac Newton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I was trying to calm myself when my mind settled on my greatest fear, defined as taphopobia. I freaked out. What was I afraid of?", "correct_answer": "Being buried alive", "incorrect_answers": ["Spiders", "Germs", "Needles"]}]